Killer Bee Rappuden: Part 2
(キラービー)アクロバット！
Acrobat!
少しはやるな… 人柱力。
So the Jinchuriki can fight,
a little.
なかなかやるが 仲よくなれぬ。
I can fight well, I'm infallible.
But to you, I can't be affable.
(ナルト)サスケの居場所
知ってんなら教えやがれ！
If you know where Sasuke is…
…tell me!
何!?
What?
(イタチ)サソリ！ デイダラ！
俺は ここまでにする。
Sasori! Deidara!
I'm done here.
(デイダラ)ここまでとは
どういう意味だ？
What do you mean, "I'm done"?
(イタチ)俺は 暁を抜ける。
I'm leaving the Akatsuki.
(デイダラ)あ～ん
何言ってやがんだ こら！
What are you saying?
(イタチ)俺は 長門とともに去る。
I'm leaving with Nagato.
あ～っ！ 逃げんな！
Don't run away!
おい！ どうする サソリの旦那？
Hey, so what are we going to do,
Sasori, my man?
どうもこうもない。
俺たちで そいつらを倒すだけだ。
Do you need to even ask?
We're going to
take them down ourselves!
(我愛羅)３対２だが。
It's three against two.
関係ない。
まあ そういうことだな。
Doesn't matter.
Guess you're right, hmm.
うん おいらの芸術を見せてやる。
I'll show them my art.
なんだ こりゃ？
(フウ)お前たち！
What is this?
Hey, you!
(フウ)
滝隠れの里で 何を騒いでいる！
Why are you causing an uproar
in the Hidden Waterfall Village?
なんだ あいつ？
Who is that?
(牛鬼)七尾の人柱力だ。
あいつが…。
That's the Seven Tails' Jinchuriki!
She is?
おい 重明！
Hey, Chomei!
(重明)フウ お仲間だ。
Fuu, they're comrades.
仲間？ あっしの？
Comrades? Of mine?
人柱力！ やつらが敵！
Hey, Jinchuriki!
They're the enemy!
何言ってるか わかんないっす。
I don't understand
what you're saying.
４対２だな。
引くぞ。
Now it's four against two.
Okay, let's retreat!
何!? よし。
What? Okay!
(デイダラ)お前ら 覚えてろよ！
I'll get you next time!
あっ！ 逃げやがった。
What? They took off!
(キラービー)滝隠れのフウだな。
You're Fuu of
the Hidden Waterfall, right?
♪♪「拳を合わせろ！」
Gimme a fist bump!
おい どうした？
おじさん 胡散臭いっす。
Hey, what's the matter?
You're kinda shady, mister.
何をいうか ベイビー。
What're you saying, baby?
♪♪「拳を合わせろ！」
C'mon, gimme a fist bump!
おい どうした？
Hey, what's the matter?!
おじさん 胡散臭いっす！
You're kinda shady, mister.
何をいうか ベイビー！ それ！
What're you saying, baby?
C'mon!
Gimme a fist bump!
♪♪「拳を合わせろ！」
嫌っす！
No!
拳を…。
嫌っす！
– A fist bump!
– No!
合わせろ！
嫌っす！
– Give it here!
– No!
合わせろ！
嫌っす！
– Give it here!
– No!
とにかく
拳を合わせてみるってばよ。
At any rate…
just give him a fist bump.
Gimme a fist bump!
♪♪「拳を合わせろ！」
嫌っす！
No!
ぶわ～!!
待て！ お前には
使命があるんだぞ！
Wait! You have a mission
to carry out!
他の里の忍の指図は
受けないっす！
I don't take orders from shinobi
from another village!
(我愛羅)俺たちは 仲間なんだ。
We're comrades.
You could even say we are friends.
あるいは
友と言ってもいいだろう。
友？ 友達？
Friends? We're friends?
そうだ。 お前は
１人なんかじゃない。
Yes. You are not alone.
フウの姉ちゃん
我愛羅には懐いたぞ！
Fuu seems to have
softened up to Gaara!
This started out
with a lot of trouble.
♪♪「展開に不服！ 結果に納得」
But I'll say,
the result is acceptable.
ビーのおっちゃん そのヒゲと
グラサンが悪いんだってばよ。
Octopops, I think your facial hair
and shades are to blame.
うるさい！ 次 いくぞ 次！
Shut up!
Let's move on to the next one!
十尾？ 何すか？ それ。
Ten Tails?
What's that?
暁が召喚した巨大兵器だ。
A gigantic weapon that
the Akatsuki summoned!
そいつが
尾獣のチャクラを吸い取ったせいで➡
It absorbed
the Tailed Beasts' chakra
みんな 全力が出せないでいる。
which is why we can't
utilize our full power.
今は 十尾のほうも
全力が出せない。
Right now, Ten Tails can't summon
its full power either.
落風城の姫が封じている。
The princess of Rappu Castle
sealed it.
だが 満月の夜
十尾の力が最大になる。
But the Ten Tails has ultimate power
on the night of the full moon.
やつらは 姫を狙って
城に攻めてくる。
They'll target the princess
and go to the castle.
俺たち 人柱力が
すべて揃わなければ➡
Unless every Jinchuriki
comes together,
we won't have a chance against it.
対抗できない。
９人で 姫と城を守るんだぜい。
The nine of us will protect
the princess and the castle…yay.
イェイ！
♪♪「拳を合わせろ！」
Gimme a fist bump.
W-What's the big idea?
い… いきなり 何するってばよ！
(九喇嘛)おい 孫悟空！ 俺たちは
敵じゃねえって そいつに伝えな。
Hey, Son Goku!
Tell him that we're not enemies!
(孫悟空)だとよ。
You heard him.
(老紫)これはすまぬ。
I'm sorry about that.
近ごろ 怪しい者どもが
現れるようになってな。
Suspicious characters
have been showing up lately.
てっきり その一味かと。
So I assumed you were one of them.
やっぱり！ そのヒゲとグラサンが
悪いんだってばよ！
I'm telling you…
it's that facial hair and shades.
No need to critique my physique.
♪♪「俺の美学 ご意見いらぬ」
怪しい者どもとは？
What do you mean by
"suspicious characters"?
正体は わからぬ。
I don't know who they are…
だが 村の子供を
さらっていくのだ。
but they've been kidnapping
children from our village.
確かに 獲物を狙う風情だな。
It definitely appears like
it's tracking prey…
重明 追っ払ってくるっす！
Chomei!
Let's chase 'em away!
承知。
Agreed.
Scale Powder!
麟粉！
あっ！
口寄せか？
It was a summoning?
(サスケ)
邪魔立てすれば容赦はしない。
If you interfere,
I'll show you no mercy.
あっ！ サスケ。
Sasuke!
ナルト お前 里を出られたのか？
Naruto…
You were able to leave the village?
お前こそ 木ノ葉の里に
帰るってばよ。
What about you?
You're coming back to the village!
お前の指図は受けない。
I don't take orders from you!
人さらいはお前の仕業か！
Are you the kidnapper?!
それがどうした？
What of it?
サスケ お前 大蛇丸の手下に
成り下がって➡
Sasuke! You've stooped so low
to be Orochimaru's underling,
こんなことやってんのかよ。
that you've started
doing things like this?
イタチの気も知らねえでよ。
And you don't even know
how Itachi's feels!
お前がイタチを語るな！
Don't you dare mention
Itachi's name!
イタチは暁を抜けて
お前を捜してんだぞ！
Itachi deserted the Akatsuki
and is looking for you!
なに!?
What?
My, my…
(大蛇丸)おやおや
人柱力がお揃いで➡
A gathering of Jinchuriki…
何をしようってのかしら。
I wonder what
you're all planning to do?
大蛇丸…。
Orochimaru…
Although you're probably helpless
もっとも 尾獣の力のほとんどが
奪われている状態で➡
because your Tailed Beast powers
have been stolen…
何もできやしないでしょうけど。
サスケ君
やっつけてしまいましょうか。
Sasuke… Shall we destroy them?
大蛇丸 俺はここまでにする。
Orochimaru… I'm done here.
えっ？ ここまでとは
どういうこと？
What? What do you mean
"I'm done"?
俺はイタチを追う。
I'm going after Itachi.
あっ！ 待てよ！
ナルト！ 使命を忘れるな！
Hey, hold it!
Naruto!
Don't forget the mission at hand!
人さらいの元凶め！
貴様はここで成敗してくれる！
You're the one
behind the kidnappings!
I'll punish you now!
Powerless Jinchuriki…
力足らずの人柱力が
大きな口をたたかないことね。
I wouldn't talk if I were you…
口寄せの術！
Summoning Jutsu!
さあ どうするのかしら？ フフフ…。
So, what are you going to do?
孫悟空！
うぉ～！
Son Goku!
大蛇丸様！
大丈夫よ。
Lord Orochimaru!
I'm okay!
うぅ… チャクラが切れやがった。
I'm out of chakra…
守鶴！
(守鶴)うぉ～！
Shukaku!
大蛇丸様！
大丈夫。
Lord Orochimaru!
I'm okay!
(フウ)行くっす！
My turn!
大蛇丸様！
大丈夫。
Lord Orochimaru!
I'm okay…
(キラービー)尾獣ラリアット！
Tailed Beast Lariat!
おぉ 大蛇丸様！
L-Lord Orochimaru!
あら 食らいすぎ。
Oh my…This is too much
even for me.
食らいやがれ！
Take this!
どうだ？
やった！
– Well?!
– We did it!
No, that's just shed skin.
いや 抜け殻だ。
Even if they're weakened,
力不足の尾獣でも➡
they still pack a punch
when they join forces.
数を揃えれば
そこそこやるようね。
さすがにしぶとい。
でも ヘロヘロしてるっす。
He's as tough as ever.
But he looks worn out!
大蛇丸様。
覚えてらっしゃい。
Lord Orochimaru…
I'll get you next time!
One down…
１つ片づいたな。
暁の陰謀を阻止するために➡
Come with us so that we can
put a stop to the Akatsuki's plot.
一緒に来てくれ。
うむ。
よし… ユギトたちと合流する。
All right.
We'll join up with Yugito
and the others.
(ユギト)三尾の人柱力 やぐらが
まだ見つからないの。
I still can't locate Yagura,
the Three Tails' Jinchuriki.
(ユギト)水の国にはいなかったわ。
He wasn't in the Land of Water.
Any clues?
(キラービー)手がかりは？
どこかの湖のほとり。
Yagura is supposedly heading to
some wetlands somewhere…
そこに やぐらが
向かったというのだけど➡
確証はないわ。
But I can't verify it.
Even if you can't, we need
all of the Jinchuriki, right?
確証がなくたって 人柱力全員が
揃わなきゃならねえんだろ？
そうだ。
すべての尾獣が揃わなければ➡
Yeah, unless every Jinchuriki
comes together,
十尾には勝てない。
やつらは 次の満月に➡
we can't beat the Ten Tails!
Those guys will begin their attack
on the next full moon…
攻撃をかけてくる。
封印が弱まるときを狙って。
targeting the time when
the seal will weaken.
あと どれくらいだ？
(ユギト)７日ほどね。
How much time do we have left?
About seven days.
Let's split up and
search for Yagura.
手分けして
やぐらを見つけるのよ。
Otherwise,
でなければ １人欠けたままで
暁と決戦になるのか。
we'll have to fight the Akatsuki
with one member short?
(キラービー)ツーマンセルで 四方に散るぜ。
We'll split up into two-man teams
and search in all four directions.
いいか みんな！
結果はともあれ➡
All right, everyone!
No matter what the result,
do not fail to gather at
Rappu Castle in seven days!
７日後には
必ず落風城に集合しろ。
行くぜ ユギト！
Let's go, Yugito!
うん？
Look forward to working with you.
(ハン)よろしくだで。
オーケー。
Okay…
なんか見えるか？
いや 霧ばかりだ。
Can you see anything?
No…
There's mist everywhere.
う～ん んじゃ
仙人モードで感知してみっか。
Then I'll check around in Sage Mode.
ん？ なんだ？
(我愛羅)どうした？
What's that?!
What's wrong?
木ノ葉の追っ手だ。
俺を捜してるんだ。
Pursuers from the Leaf…
They're looking for me!
乗れ。
Get on!
どこも人柱力を 自由に
させておきたくないようだな。
It seems no one wants to give
Jinchuriki their freedom.
ああ。
Yeah…
They treat us like dangerous vessels
that contain Tailed Beasts.
まるで尾獣の入った
危険な入れ物扱いだ。
We're not dangerous,
and neither are Tailed Beasts!
尾獣も俺たちも
危険なんかじゃねえってばよ。
(ハン)三尾の人柱力 やぐらだな。
It's Yagura,
the Three Tails' Jinchuriki.
♪♪「拳を合わせろ！」
Gimme a fist bump.
(やぐら)嫌だ。
I refuse.
磯撫 そいつに伝えてくれ。
Isobu, tell him!
確かにこの２人
見た目は怪しいが➡
Without a doubt,
these two look suspicious,
but they are Jinchuriki friends.
人柱力の仲間なんだとな。
(やぐら)
人柱力に仲間なんかいない。
Jinchuriki don't have friends.
俺たちは 人柱力というだけで
人に恐れられ➡
Just being Jinchuriki fills people
with fear, resentment and hatred.
憎まれ いみ嫌われる。
時に同じ里の者に命を狙われる。
Sometimes, we're hunted by
people of our own village.
それが人柱力の運命だ。
That's our fate as Jinchuriki!
そんなのはまっぴらだから
俺は１人でここにいる。
So I want no part of this.
I'll stay here by myself.
お前の力が必要だ。
We need your power.
Go away!
帰れ。
一緒に来い それがお前の運命だ。
Come with us.
That is your destiny.
俺にこれ以上の運命を強要するな。
Don't force anymore destiny on me.
力ずくか。
Do you want me to force him?
お前は手を出すな。
Stay out of this.
俺たちは 同じ人柱力だ。
We are all Jinchuriki.
人柱力という運命を➡
The fate forced on me as a Jinchuriki
is more than enough for me!
背負わせられただけで
もうたくさんだ！
背負わされたんだろうが
なんだろうが➡
Whether it was forced on you or not,
this is your fate!
そいつがお前の運命なんだよ！
うるさい！
Shut up!
バカ野郎 この野郎。
Fool, ya fool…
背負った以上は その運命を
貫くしかねえだろう！
As long as it's your destiny,
you've got to see it through!
うお～！
ビー。
Bee?!
(やぐら)お前…。
You!
We're the same Jinchuriki as you.
俺たちは 同じ人柱力。
恐れない 憎まない 嫌わない。
We don't fear you.
We don't resent you.
And we don't hate you.
♪♪「拳を合わせろ！」
Gimme a fist bump.
(キラービー)お前の力を
俺たちと合わせてくれ。
Let's combine your power
with ours.
(ウタカタ)間もなく満月の夜になる。
It will soon be the night
of the full moon.
なんで 言い出しっぺのビーの
おっちゃんたちが来ねえんだよ。
How come Octopops isn't here?
He's the one who planned all of this.
１人欠けるどころか
３人も欠けるとは。
Not just one person is missing,
but three.
これで なんとかなるっすか？
Will we be able to pull this off?
ならないだろうな。
Probably not.
どうすんだよ？ ユギトのおばちゃん。
おばちゃん？
What should we do, Aunty Yugito?
"Aunty"?
あ？ いや… ユギトのお姉さん。
Oh, I mean… Sister Yugito.
ビーたちが必ず来ると信じて
持ちこたえるしかない。
We have no choice but to have faith
that Bee and the others will come.
現れたぞ。
お？
They've appeared.
ゆけ！
Go!
(みんな)おぉ～！
俺たちも行こうぜ うん！
Let's go too, hmm.
No need to rush.
Wait for the moon to rise.
慌てることはない。
月の出るのを待て。
(みんな)わぁ～！
暁の下忍どもが来るっす！
The Akatsuki genin are attacking!
防ぐよ 城内へ一歩も入れるな！
Defend the castle!
Don't let a single one get inside!
(みんな)わぁ～！
水遁 泡沫の術！
Water Style: Bubble Jutsu!
溶遁 灼河流岩の術！
Lava Style: Scorching Rocks Jutsu!
Wind Style: Rasen Shuriken!
風遁 螺旋手裏剣！
(我愛羅)ハァ～！
やっぱり俺たちが出ないとダメだろ。
うん！
Looks like we have to
get involved, hmm?
それには及ばない。
That's not necessary.
外道魔像！
The Gedo Statue?!
They're gonna use that to attack!
あれで攻撃するつもりっすよ。
全力とはいかないが
これでも十分だろ。
It won't be at full strength,
but it should suffice.
芸術性は カケラもねえけどな。
But there isn't a single fragment
of art to it though.
(ウタカタ)尾獣玉！
It's a Tailed Beast Bomb!
クソ！ 今のわしらには
撃てねえってのに！
Damn! The way I am right now,
I can't take it down.
みんな 大丈夫か!?
Is everyone okay?
今だ！ かかれ！
Now! Charge!
(みんな)わ～！
ま まずいっす！
(ハン)蒸気驀進！
Th-This isn't good!
Steam Dash!
でや～！
あれは！
仲間たちよ！
That's...!
Friends!
この俺が来たからには
もう大丈夫だ！
Now that I'm here,
you don't have to worry!
待たせたな。
おっせえよ！ ビーのおっちゃん！
Sorry to keep you waiting!
You're late, Octopops!
でも 三尾のやぐらを
見つけたのね！
But you found Yagura of the Three Tails!
Yeah! All nine of us are together!
おう！ これで９人 揃ったぞ！
さあ 人柱力たち！
Okay, Jinchuriki!
拳を突き上げろ！
Raise your fists!
(みんな)お～！
なんだありゃ!?
What is that?!
One Tail.
一尾。
二尾！
Two Tails.
Three Tails.
三尾！
四尾。
Four Tails.
Five Tails.
五尾。
六尾。
Six Tails.
Seven Tails.
七尾っす！
八尾。
Eight Tails.
九尾だってばよ！
And Nine Tails, y'know!
俺たち人柱力！ 今ここに立つ！
We are the Jinchuriki
who stand before you!
う… なんかあれ… 芸術っぽいぞ。
That's kind of artsy!
今更 ９人揃おうが無駄だ。
It doesn't matter at this point
if they're assembled together.
(みんな)はっ！
おいおい 向こうも尾獣玉だ。
それがどうした。
Hey, hey…
There are Tailed Beast Bombs
over there too.
What of it?
Shukaku!
(我愛羅)守鶴！
(ユギト)又旅！
Matatabi!
(やぐら)磯撫！
(老紫)孫悟空！
Isobu!
Son Goku!
(ハン)穆王！
(ウタカタ)犀犬！
Kokuo!
Saiken!
(フウ)重明！
(キラービー)牛鬼！
九喇嘛！
おわっ！ やべえ！
これで勝ったと思うなよ！
次は ぜってえ倒してやるぜ！
うん！
ふう しんでえな。
また チャクラ切れだぜ。
勝ったわね。
やったぜ。
ああ だが➡
尾獣の力を取り戻さないかぎり➡
真の勝利とはいえないぜ。
もっとも…。
今日のところは大勝利！
ハハハハ！
フフフ…。
(キラービー)フフフ。
すごい人で。
もう 皆さん すばらしい。
あったかいですなぁ。
あったかいですね。
今日も 張り切っていこう。
はい。
北島先生に
お願いがあるんですけども。
お願い？
はい。
お金なら…。
ないよ？
北島先生の 『風雪ながれ旅』を➡
ご一緒させて
いただけないでしょうか。
氷川さん。
はい。
よろしくお願いします。
よろしくお願いします！
やった～！
やりましょう！